Adolphe Kalisa

Web Developer - Student

My name is Adolphe Kalisa. I was born in Kigali, Rwanda on November 12th, 1997. I currently live in Kimironko, Kigali and I am enrolled in Southern New Hampshire University in the Associate of Arts in General Studies with a Specialization in Business.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Journalist: Media Club LDK

(2014-2016)

Secretary: The East African Community LDK (2015-2016) Member: Peace and Love Proclaimers (2015-2017) Web Developer: Kepler Hackathon Program(2018present)

EDUCATION

2002-2010: Kigali Parents' School

2011-2016: Lycee de Kigali **2017-present:** Southern New

Hampshire University

SKILLS

- Advanced in Microsoft Suite (Word, Excel, PPT)
- Web Development
- Web Design
- Professional Competencies (Prosocial behavior, conflict resolution, etc)
- Typing (50 wpm)



adolphekalisa15@gmail.com

+250-783-052-921

CERTIFICATES

EAC Certificate

EducationUSA Certificate

Media Club Certificate

PLP Certificate

LANGUAGES

English: Advanced

Kinyarwanda: Advanced **French:** Intermediate **Swahili:** Intermediate

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Coding
- Playing and Watching Basketball
- Travelling
- Listening to Music